learnrealenglish.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - Learn Real English

**Learn Real English LLC** is serious about protecting your online privacy. This Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as a user of our website. We understand your concern regarding the use of your personal information and we hope this information will enable you to feel secure about using our website.

**Information about our Organization and Web site**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Learn Real English LLC. We are based in The USA.Our principal activity is: English Language EducationOur privacy policy covers Learn Real English LLC and its Web site: LearnRealEnglish.com

Organization Name: | Learn Real English LLC  
---|---  
Address: | 1706 Church Street #1233  
City, Zip: | San Francisco, 94131  
State: | California  
Country: | USA  
Controllers: | Kristin Dodds, Allen Hoge, Joseph Weiss  
Web Sites(s): | LearnRealEnglish.com  
  
**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web site**

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.Our Web site also includes a link to:

  * Google Adwords

Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors.

**Automatic Collection of Information**

**We may use cookies on our Web site.**

We may automatically log personal data and we may link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

**Data Collection**

We collect the personal data that you may knowingly volunteer while using our services and purchasing our products.

We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except 1. To the extent necessary to complete that order or to provide services where the outside party is acting on our behalf and has no independent right to use the information we provide (e.g., third-party shipping, business analytics, or customer support ), or 2. To successors in title to our business, or 3. In accordance with legal and regulatory requirements, or 4. As necessary, in Learn Real English’s sole discretion, to protect the perceived rights, safety and property of Learn Real English, users of our websites, and the public.

We do not and never will sell your information.

We also may automatically collect and/or track information collected from Web page HTTP headers from your Web activity on our website (e.g., IP address, type of client computer, and type of Web browser).

We also collect E-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Learn Real English LLC via e-mail.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected.

We may use cookies to serve our Google remarketing campaign so that third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, you can choose to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Use of Collected Data**

We use the collected data to create content on our website that we believe will interest visitors to our website.

We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners.

We may also use this data to improve our site, for statistical analysis and for marketing and promotional purposes. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future correspondence regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online.

By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.

**Your Opt-Out Rights**

You have the right to opt-out of receiving future correspondence from us by:

  * Clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email we send you
  * Sending an email to info@learnrealenglish.com requesting that you be opted-out of future correspondence

**Confidentiality / Security**

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * unauthorized access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorized modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us, by sending an email (members@learnrealenglish.com ): whether we are keeping personal data about you.

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. – although we may before require proof of your identity -.We will provide the information without any charge. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**Privacy Compliance**

We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy instrument.

**Privacy Support** If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:

| Contacts  
---|---  
Names : | Kristin Dodds, Allen Hoge, Joseph Weiss  
Department : |   
Address : | 1706 Church Street #1233, San Francisco, CA 94131  
Phone Number : | (415) 287-0419  
Fax Number : |   
Email address : | members@learnrealenglish.com
